Once again, Yukari Resort Gero Onsen
We are pleased to bring you the following with the cooperation of Saichouraku!
Hi!
It's time for the Hajime Gakuen!
Yay! We are here at the chorus village in Shimoronsen.
The choral village here was originally located in Shirakawa, but about 10 oats moved here to form this village.
The village is made up of about 10 oats that used to live on the Baiheon River.
The moment you enter, the atmosphere changes completely, and you feel like you've gone back in time.
I feel like I've been transported back in time!
Let's just go with it. I felt right at home and we were talking naturally.
It suits you, doesn't it? What am I becoming now?
Show a little more face. An egret.
I'm an egret. What are you supposed to be?
I wonder if it's a girl I'm a person I'm a girl
I'm going to enjoy the chorus village today
Kinkong kankong
The paintings are really beautiful
We can go inside, right? Let's go in
This is really amazing... it's made by human hands.
What's going on?
Please, excuse me.
It's like a museum.
Straw cage.
The smallest straw cage in Japan.
Oh, this? I mean this!
So cute!
Smaller than a go-en-ball.
I used to live in a place like this.
"People's Fungi.
What's a fungus?
It's a repellent against insects.
Oh, a barrel! A square barrel.
It's a keg to store sake.
What is it?
No, no, no...
There are many kinds of barrels.
There's this creaking sound, too.
There's so much noise here!
You know, I'm getting worried.
What do you use it for? Suntan lotion.
You mean an iron?
That's great. That's an iron.
An ink iron.
The shape hasn't changed much.
The iron has always been this way.
There's a doll corner.
Wow! Beautiful!
Clay dolls?
Are they made of clay?
Let's find my favorite doll!
What do you think she'll look like? But they're all so bright.
He's a little bit overestimated.
He's so cool.
My guess is this girl.
What's your guess, Nao?
The little big guy.
Is that him? Is he on it?
The top one looks like a chick.
That's funny.
It's a beautiful day.
The trees are so tall.
They'll grow and grow and grow.
It's going to look great on the outside.
Nao, stand there for a second.
Where?
Stand over there.
It's easy to forget about the flies.
But you know what? Just being there is enough to make you fly.
Here we go! Cheese!
Mokka! Cheese!
Yeah!
Oh, my gosh!
What is this place?
Weasel.
Itakura's place.
It's got "Itakura" written all over it.
Is it some kind of storage place?
Oh, it's small.
Is it a place to keep tools or something?
Excuse me for disturbing you.
It belongs to the Higashiyama family.
They say it's a warehouse for storing grain and farming implements.
Yes.
It's a warehouse.
Oh, there's a second floor, too?
Ah, the former Odo Family Residence.
National Important Cultural Property.
Hee...
A building.
Wow, let's go in!
Wow, Housan, that's amazing!
Here's a room. Make yourself at home.
Wow, make yourself at home.
Irori!
Wow, there are lots of dolls again!
I see.
It's Kintaro.
It's true.
I found Kintaro.
He's so cute.Cute.
Isn't that happiness?
Yes, it is.
Happiness! I found happiness.
What a surprise. I thought there were people here.
I'm scared.
I'm so surprised.
Let's go there.
Excuse me. I'm sorry to bother you.
It's a nice house.
Buddha and Demon. It's so splendid.
Amazing.
The porch.
The yard and garden are lovely.
It has a pattern.
Huh, nice.
It's nice. It makes me feel calm.
It calms my mind.
Then let's go this way.
Yes.
Wow, there are a lot of people.
Wow!
What is it?
Housewives.
They're all women, for sure.
Super udder. Strong udder.
What's going on? What are you doing here?
I think it's some kind of sewing thing, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
They have kimonos and stuff.
I see.
So, do women work here?
Right.
Yes.
Water... Oh, this is a watering hole!
Watering hole.
Yeah, oh, it's really running water.
It already did.
Oh, family meeting?
Mm-hmm.
What meeting room? There's a bunch of stuff over here.
Is there two? No, there's a lot.
Well, it's a big family house.
It's big.
Oh, a lot of old houses have steep stairs, but... old houses...
This one's really steep. A ladder is steep, too.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. It's just a ladder.
Watch your step.
The roof is close.
The view is amazing!
It's great, Housan!
Let's take a picture here.
Yoo-hoo! It feels so good!
Amazing!
I didn't know old houses
You have all kinds of equipment in your old house.
How did you do that?
Hey, it's amazing.
Hey, Aho, here's some money.
What's that?
Ten thousand, twenty thousand.
Oh, it's really money.
I don't know why.
He's rich.
What's wrong with him?
Hey, stay that way.
I've been doing a lot of work for you.
He's very rich.
I don't have any explanation for this money.
Maybe everyone put in a little bit of it.
That's possible.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Shall we go down? Oh, silkworms.
Larvae.
Let's go in here.
Let's go.
There's something tasty.
Oh, it looks a little bit like a God's-viewing place
It's nice.
Oh, there's a slide and stuff.
Oh, a slide!
I want to go, I want to go!
I haven't gone down a slide in a long time!
What's this?
There's something written on it in china.
It's written on it.
It's like a votive tablet.
Isn't it too stylish? Ceramic?
Hey...
I'm so excited to go.
I wonder...
Eating Japanese sweets in a place like this has a great atmosphere, doesn't it?
Oh, we're outside...
Oh, they didn't come this way.
Maybe it's this way.
It's a nice walking course.
It's great this time of year.
Hey.
Is this it?Is this it?
Here it is!
We're here!
That's the entrance, and this is the entrance?
Finally, we're in.
We're at Mr. Van Coan's.
Well, let's go in.
It's time for a short break.
Hello, please.
Hello!
It's so warm!
Wow! The view is amazing. Thank you.
Here you go. Bancoa Ambis.
Wow! Thank you very much.
Cute.
Cute. It's got a lot of stuff in it.
I wonder what it is.
I'll try it.
So I should just pour this on it?
Please eat it with kuro miso.
I'll eat it.
Cute! Wait a minute!
This is fly!
Yes, it is!
If you don't take it here, when will you take it?
Okay.
Yeah, that's good.
All right, all right.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Well, where shall I start?
I guess I can eat this red bean paste.
Yes, go ahead!
What is this yellowish green color on top of this red bean paste?
I wonder what's coated on it.
It's sweet potato on top.
Oh, sweet potatoes?
It's a boiled sweet potato.
I see...
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Yes.
Yeah.
It's a year-old shop.
Elegantly sweet.
Oh!
Delicious.
I took so many things.
Is it a white ball?
I wonder if it's shiratama.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Is it good? Yes! Mochi-mochi!
Now there's green tea flavor, shiratama, and... what's this?
The colorful ones are shiratama... and the orange ones are shiratama with tomato juice.
Huh! Tomato juice? Yes...
The green one has mugwort and the white one has tofu.
Tofu! It's tofu! Now tofu...
It's definitely... it could be... tofu!
Matcha is now...
What is this? The red one in the middle...
The red one is tomatoes with mugwort, dipped in honey.
It's tomatoes! Tomato!
Wow! Looks delicious!
Can I eat a tomato then? Eat it!
I can't imagine what it's like, but...
So these are mini tomatoes! Yes, they are!
Bon appétit!
Tomatoes!
Tomatoes and molasses go well together?
That's so interesting!
The texture is still there, the raw tomato texture and taste is still there, but the sweetness is still in the middle.
The tomatoes are still inside, so there is just the right balance of sweetness. The sweetness.
Delicious!
What is this? Is it a warabi mochi?
This is sashimi konnyaku from Yaokichi, a konnyaku shop on Ieji, covered with powder.
It's konnyaku!
Bon appétit!
What is it?
The texture is amazing. It's so soft and smooth.
What do you mean?
Even if it's konjac, this is the first time I've had this texture.
The elasticity is amazing.
It's a strange konjac.
It's delicious.
I'm really looking forward to all kinds of things.
It's more elastic than warabi-mochi.
I wonder if it's that.
The surface tension.
Yes. It has a little texture.
Yes, it does.
Let's drink matcha.
That sounds good.
Delicious.Delicious.
I don't have much of a taste for it, but I'm turning it on anyway.
Japan is nice.
Yes, it is. Are you feeling Japan?
I feel Japan. This view, sweet anmitsu and green powdered tea make me happy.
Excuse me. Apple juice is amazing.
I can feel the pulp in this apple juice.
It makes me happy.
Anmitsu in this air.
It's even more special.
It's the best!
It's so good!
It was so good!
Thank you for the food.
Hey, do you want to take a look around some more?
I just saw a slide.
You know...
I'm sure you'd love to go down that slide.
What's that?
You can already see it on that side.
Oh, that.
That's it.
Oh, it's so long!
Isn't it really long?
So long!
The forest slide.
Shall we go this way?
Forest slide
Wait!
Wait! Nanny, wait!
Wait! Nachan, wait!
Nachan, wait!
We're at the slide, but...
We've come so far...
We've climbed so high.
It's so high.
We're on a mountain.
If we can go down to the bottom, it must be a long slide.
Yeah.
Put this butt seat down.
Put it down.
I'm gonna lay it down and go down.
It looked like a roller, right?
It was like a roller.
Heh, at my age, I don't ski very often, so...
I'm in.
100 yen.
Okay, I'll go.
Okay, I'm going!
I'm going now?
Okay.
Whee!
Oh, he's slowing down!
He's slowing down!
Aah!
That hurts!
Come on, baby, hurry up!
Aaah!
The picture...
Hey!
Look at you having fun!
Have fun!
Yes!
I guess I'd better get going too, huh?
Yay! I'm so excited!
Let's go!
When was the last time you went on the slide?
Wow!
He's saying something.
I guess I'll go then.
I wonder if I'm getting this?
I'm off!
GO!
Woooo!
Eeeee!
I'm good!
Woooo!
Wahhh!
Watch out!
The next one's coming up.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Wow.
Oh.
Waah.
Ha!
Scary
Rapid
Wow.
Fun!
Wait, if you want to get this out, it's really fast!
I think it's going to be really fast.
I'm still a little flustered.
My body's vibrating.
Okay, I'm off.
I'm off!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, fast, fast, fast! Whoo!
Woooo!Wahhh!
Wah! Wait! Wahhh!
Aah! Wait! This place is going crazy! It's going crazy! It's going crazy!
Deceleration: ~~~~~
Huh! Aah! Aaah! Aaah!
Aaah! Aaah! Wait!
Wait! It's coming off!
Push it out!
What?
It's coming off.
That was fun! Oh, man!
There's so many places.
You know, it's like, of course, you get to know the old days.
I mean, you get to eat good food, and the scenery.
The slides, I didn't think there was any activity!
And it's so long and fun!
So I was able to take a lot of pictures of the projection scene.
Here are the ones I chose!
Well, I got a good picture!
I got it!
Bye bye!
It was a great memory!
It was the best school trip ever!
It was so much fun!
I would like to come back to Gassho Village again!
Please come visit us again!
Bye bye!
It's time for Hatsuchi News!
We, Team Hatsuchi, are now on a free live tour!
We are now on a free live tour!
We'll be performing live, and of course we'll be holding special events.
Please come and see us!
And on June 3, we are going to hold
Yuzuki's Hair Festival
Yuzuki will be hosting a festival called Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
That's the third time you've held this event.
Yes, this is the third time.
And this time it's at the new ZEPP Shinjuku.
ZEPP Shinjuku, which is a brand-new venue.
This will be our first time to visit ZEPP Shinjuku!
Yuzuki will shine very brightly!
Please come and visit us!
We look forward to seeing you there!
And what can I say?
This summer, July 22nd.
We will be holding an Orca Festival at Nagoya Castle!
Killer Whale!
It's our one-man show for the summer.
Last year, we came back after a long absence.
In the open air, at Nagoya Castle.
The place where we started.
Yes, Nagoya Castle is where we made our debut on the street.
So I'm really looking forward to seeing Orca-sama at the place of my memories.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Just thinking about it makes me heavy.
I know, it's awful.
I'm so excited!
After all, it's really hot in Nagoya in the summer.
It's really hot in Nagoya.
I want to do a live show that won't lose to the heat.
I'm looking forward to doing a live show that won't let the heat get the better of me.
Please come to Nagoya Castle on July 22nd!
We're looking forward to seeing you there!
That's all for now.